The war was just the beginning.
WarHunt is a action, horror, thriller film directed by Mauro Borrelli.
military cargo plane loses control and violently crashes behind
enemy lines in the middle of the German black forest.
Major Johnson sends a squad of his bravest soldiers on a rescue mission to retrieve the
top-secret material the plane was carrying, led by Sergeants Brewer and Walsh.
They soon discover hanged Nazi soldiers and other dead
bodies bearing ancient, magical symbols.
Suddenly their compasses fail, their perceptions twist and straying from the group leads to
profound horrors as they are attacked by a powerful, supernatural force.
Sergeant Brewer, played by Robert Knepper.
Walsh, played by Jackson Rathbone.
Major Johnson, played by Mickey Rourke.
Venefica, played by Aglaya Tarasova.
Stria, played by Anna Paliga.
Hexe, played by Lou Stassen.
Warhunt is a 2022 American horror film directed by
Mauro Borrelli and starring Mickey Rourke.
The film explores themes of witch, world war ii, witchcraft.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.